HARISH HONA

Madhyapur-Thimi - 8, Bhaktapur, Nepal | contact@harishhona.com.np | harishhona.com.np | <a

WEB DEVELOPER

A practical web developer with significant experience in front-end development, SEO, and graphic design. I have worked as a freelancer and am currently serving as a webmaster SEO specialist at Mushroom Seed Nepal & Research Center.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Webmaster and SEO Specialist | Mushroom Seed Nepal & Research Center

July 2023 - present

- Manage website functionality ensuring optimal performance using Wordpress
- Implement SEO strategies that significantly and improve search engine rankings including writing blogs

Video Editor | Upwork Freelance

July 2023 - Aug 2023

• Collaborated with clients and deliver compelling visual narratives that engage the audiences.

SKILLS

- Web Development (HTML, CSS, JS)
- Search Engine Optimization
- Social Media Marketing

- Efficiency Under Pressure
- Critical Thinking
- Website Management

EDUCATION

Bachelor in Computer Application | Samriddhi College

Dec 2023 - present

Lokanthali, Bhaktapur

+2 | Khwopa Secondary School

Aug 2021 - Sept 2023

Dekocha, Bhaktapur

SEE | Himchuli Academy

SEE Batch 2020

Dhuncho-pakha, Bhaktapur

INTERESTS

- Video Editing
- Video Games
- Blogging

- Movies & TV Shows
- Travel
- Table Tennis

LICENSES AND CERTIFICATES

- Programming with JavaScript | Meta (Issued Sep 2024)
- Intra-college Hackathon 2024 | Samriddhi IT Club (Issued Sep 2024)
- Linux Fundamentals | Red Hat Academy (Issued Sep 2024)
- Responsive Web Design | FreeCodeCamp (Issued Jan 2024)